BIRVA SHAH

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: +91 9427776960

Email: shahbirva927@gmail.com

Address: 42, Shaktinagar Soc., Mehsana, Gujarat, India-384001

PERSONAL PROFILE

A versatile leader and a vibrant spirit striving to explore with a ceaseless drive to learn. Propelled to research and intending to create soothing and thrilling projects with a goal of maximum usability that can make an impact around.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- User Interface Design(UI)
- · Wireframing & Prototyping
- User Experience Design(UX)
- · html, css, js, php
- Graphic Designing (Figma)
- Working knowledge of C, C++, Python, Java, C#
- Quality Testing

OTHER SKILLS

- Can easily grasp concepts and work on various field of projects
- Strong Work Ethic
- Positive attitude towards learning and exploring
- · Detail oriented
- Creative

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Anchoring
- · Content Writing
- Drawing
- Travelling
- Photography
- Classical Dance Bharatnatyam
- Sports

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/birva-shah-68b4461a2/

Medium: medium.com/@shahbirva9999

WORK EXPERIENCE

QUALITY ANALYSIS AND UI/UX DESIGNING

Meditab Software India Pvt. Ltd. | 03/01/2022 - Current

- · Quality Analysis
 - WEBIMS-IEMO/ Dr. Catalyst EHR (Technology: Manual Testing)
- UI/ UX Designing (Tools Used: Figma, Canva, Vectary)
 - BillrMD Website Mockup
 - Dr. Catalyst EHR product logo and mobile application designs

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN

Elegant MicroWeb Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | 05/2021 - 07/2021

• Sahna Consultancy Website Mockup (Technology: UI/UX Design-Figma)

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Elegant MicroWeb Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | 04/2020 - 05/2020

- Administration Panel for WeWork | Project: WeWork-GLR(Language: php, bootstrap, HTML, CSS)
- · CRUD operations and User Management

EDUCATION HISTORY

CHARUSAT UNIVERSITY

DEVANG PATEL INSTITUTE OF ADVANCE TECHNOLOGY AND RESEARCH

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Engineering (2018–2022)

- CGPA- 9.69 (1st Rank in the Department of Computer Engineering)
- Google Developer Student Clubs- CHARUSAT Core Team (2020-2021)
- IEEE Member (2019-2020)
- Certificates
 - Attended Gesture Robotics Workshop-IIT, BOMBAY(2020)
 - 30- Days of Google Cloud (2020)
 - Foundation of User Experience(UX) Design (Coursera-2021)
 - Start the UX Design Process- Empathize, Define, Ideate (Coursera)
 - Programming for Python (Coursera)

DIVINE CHILD SCHOOL

Graduated Class of 2018 (HSC)

- Percentage: 82.2%
- Nominated for the best allrounder of school -2017

Graduated Class of 2016(SSC)

- CGPA: 10
- House Captain 2015-16
- Anchored Events